<?xml version='1.0' encoding='ISO-8859-1' ?>
<!DOCTYPE toc PUBLIC "-//Sun Microsystems Inc.//DTD JavaHelp TOC Version 1.0//EN" 
 "http://java.sun.com/products/javahelp/toc_1_0.dtd"> 
<toc version="1.0"> 
<tocitem>&#26032;&#30528;&#35352;&#20107;
    <tocitem target="a0000000002">2017&#24180;&#24230;
        <tocitem target="a0000000003">Depaoli & van de Schoot (2017). Improving transparency and replication in Bayesian statistics: The WAMBS-checklist. Psychological Methods, 22(2), 240-261. 
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000004">van de Schoot, Winter, Ryan, Zondervan-Zwijnenburg, & Depaoli (2017). A systematic review of Bayesian articles in psychology: The last 25 years. Psychological Methods, 22(2), 217-239.
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000005">Hoijtink & Chow (2017). Bayesian hypothesis testing: Editorial to the special issue on Bayesian data analysis. Psychological Methods, 22(2), 211-216.
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000006">Pek, J., & Flora, D. B. (in press). Reporting effect sizes in original psychological research: A discussion and tutorial. Psychological Methods. 
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000007">Cohen, B. H. (2017). Why the resistance to statistical innovations?: A comment on Sharpe (2013). Psychological Methods, 22(1), 204-210.
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000008">Anderson, S. F., & Maxwell, S. E. (2017). Addressing the &#8220;replication crisis": Using original studies to design replication studies with appropriate statistical power. Multivariate Behavioral Research, Published Online
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000009">Tang, Y., Cook, T. D., & Kisbu-Sakarya, Y. (in press). Statistical power for the comparative regression discontinuity design with a nonequivalent comparison group. Psychological Methods. http://psycnet.apa.org/doi/10.1037/met0000118
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000010">Usami, S. (2017). Generalized sample size determination formulas for investigating contextual effects by a three-level random intercept model. Psychometrika, 82(1), 133-157. https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11336-016-9532-y
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000011">Höhn, H., & Chiu, C. (2017). A procedure for assessing the completeness of the Q-matrix of cognitively diagnostic tests. Psychometrika, 82(1), 112-132. http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11336-016-9536-7
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000012">McClelland, G. H., Irwin, J. R., Disatnik, D., & Sivan, L. (2017). Multicollinearity is a red herring in the search for moderator variables: A guide to interpreting moderated multiple regression models and a critique of Iacobucci, Schneider, Popovich, and Bakamitsos (2016). Behavior Research Methods, 49(1), 394-402. http://link.springer.com/article/10.3758/s13428-016-0785-2
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000013">Bishara, A. J., & Hittner, J. B. (2017). Confidence intervals for correlations when data are not normal. Behavior Research Methods, 49(1), 294-309. http://link.springer.com/article/10.3758/s13428-016-0702-8
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000014">Rights, J. D., & Sterba, S. K. (in press). A framework of R-squared measures for single-level and multilevel regression. Psychological Methods. http://psycnet.apa.org/doi/10.1037/met0000139
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000015">Lai, M. H. C., Kwok, O., & Hsiao, Y. (in press). Finite population correction for two-level hierarchical linear models. Psychological Methods. http://psycnet.apa.org/psycinfo/2017-12025-001/
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000016">Scherer, E. A., Huang, L., & Shrier, L. A. (2017). Application of correlated time-to-event models to ecological momentary assessment data. Psychometrika, 82(1), 223-244. http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11336-016-9495-z
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000017">Michiels, B., Heyvaert, M., Meulders, A., & Onghena, P. (2017). Confidence intervals for single-case effect size measures based on randomization test inversion. Behavior Research Methods, 49(1), 363-381. 
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000018">Manolov, R., & Patrick, O. (in press). Analyzing data from single-case alternating treatment designs. Psychological Methods. http://psycnet.apa.org/doi/10.1037/met0000133
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000019">Finnigan, K. M., & Vazire, S. (in press). The incremental validity of average state self-reports over global self-reports of personality. Journal of Personality and Social Psychology
            
        </tocitem><tocitem target="a0000000020">Lüdtke, O., Robitzsch, A., & Grund, S. (2017). Multiple Imputation of Missing Data in Multilevel Designs: A Comparison of Different Strategies. Psychological Methods, 22(1), 141-165.
            
        </tocitem>
    </tocitem>
</tocitem>
</toc>